ringsidecollectibles.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Ringside Collectibles

Ringside Collectibles Inc. and its subsidiaries respect your right to privacy. We may change or add to this privacy policy at any time without notice, so we encourage you to review it periodically. Ringside Collectibles reserves the right to vary this policy at any time. By purchasing our items or using our services or website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the following privacy policy.

\- We collect any name and address that you list in terms of shipping and billing and file it for record of order.

\- All credit card transactions immediately withdraw funds and are processed through a secure third party. Only the last four digits of your credit card number will be filed for reference.

\- When placing an order, your e-mail will be automatically be signed up for our mailing list. E-Mails are generally sent 2-3 times a week updating you on the latest wrestling action figures at Ringside Collectibles. To be removed from the email list, please make sure that you have "Unsubscribe" in the subject line and send your email address to new_figures@wrestlingfigures.com

\- Absolutely none of your information including and not limited to name, address, credit card or items purchased is sold or given to any commercial third party. Any documents or invoices with customer information are shredded.

\- We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. Pursuant to COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information or accept orders online from children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information or placed an order without their consent, please contact us at 1-866-993-3448, by e-mail at cs@ringsidecollectibles.net, and we will remove the information and/or cancel the order.

If you have an questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please **[Contact Us](http://www.ringsidecollectibles.com/mm5/merchant.mvc?Screen=CTUS&Store_Code=rsc)**

Shop Products

Shop By Superstar
